50,000 bands and 1 disgusting bathroom.
CBGB is a drama, music film directed by Randall Miller.
A look at New York's dynamic punk rock scene through the lens of the ground-breaking Lower East Side
club started by eccentric Hilly Kristal in 1973 which launched thousands of bands.
Hilly Kristal, played by Alan Rickman.
Cheetah Chrome, played by Rupert Grint.
Debbie Harry, played by Malin Åkerman.
Terry Ork, played by Johnny Galecki.
Genya Ravan, played by Stana Katic.
Lisa Kristal, played by Ashley Greene.
CBGB is a 2013 American biographical drama film about
the former New York music venue CBGB.
It follows the story of Hilly Kristal's New York club from its concept as a venue for Country, Bluegrass and
Blues (CBGB) to what it ultimately became: the birthplace of underground rock 'n' roll and punk.
The film uses devices such as comic book-style panels, as well as onscreen
text to identify important figures in the punk movement.
The film explores themes of new york city, night
life, punk rock, talking head, blondie.
The tone is emotional.